Mandeep Mahadev Dalavi



mandeepdalavi@gmail.com



+91 7498287975



linkedin.com/in/mandeep-d-a51590135



https://github.com/MandeepDalavi

Summary

Experienced Technical background with a demonstrated history of working in the non-profit organization &enterprise management industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Java, C++, Python, Android Development, Website Development, Management, Time Management, and Teamwork. Strong information technology professional studying B. E. Computer Engineering focused on Computer Science & Cyber Security.

Experience



Co-Founder & Director

Always Sahi Solutions Private Limited Apr 2021 - Present (1 month +)



Vice President

Bondsocially Foundation Jan 2021 - Present (4 months +)



Web Developer

Sam Enterprises

May 2020 - Aug 2020 (4 months)

Built the basic structure of their website and helped them to publish it by purchasing Domain & Hosting Services.

Technical Manager

Bondsocially Foundation May 2019 - Apr 2020 (1 year)

Education



Savitribai Phule Pune University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering 2019 - 2023



Army Public School, Dighi

12th, Science 2018 - 2019 (Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics, English (Core), Informatics Practices)

Licenses & Certifications

Google's Fundamentals of Digital Marketing - Google

L2Q 85B DMA

IS Ethical Hacking - Internshala

D1ED4C1D-6168-E600-E7DE-10681D4DF4C2

Maharashtra State Certificate in Information Technology - Maharashtra Knowledge

Corporation Limited (MKCL) 19-4025574

Certificate Course in Programming - Disha Computer Institute - India

16010131915

Skills

C++ • Java • Web Development • Programmer • Computer Engineering • Information Technology • Social Services • Social Media Marketing • Android • Python (Programming Language)

Honors & Awards

Student of the Year 2019 - Heyfolio

Jan 2020

was found to be the most Enthusiastic and Result oriented.

Certificate of Achievement - Major League Hacking

Dec 2018

Won 1st place in Major League Hacking's 2018 Local Hack Day on campus among 30 students bymaking my first software i.e. Legionnaire-OS (Android Simulator).

Ref:

https://devpost.com/MandeepDalavi

https://github.com/MandeepDalavi/Legionnaire-OS

The Best-In-The-Game Talent Hunt - Vidyartha

Nov 2017

Topped the People & Business Category in Vidyartha's Best-in-the-Game Talent Hunt 2017